RG 079:005, Department of Environmental Protection: Air, Waste and Water
Connecticut State Library
- Series 14. Bureau of Water Management, 1920-1979
  - Permitting, Enforcement, and Remediation Division, 1928-1979; bulk 1969-1977
    - Correspondence Files, 1997-050
      - Stamford (Box 109)
        - High Ridge Park (Box 110)
        - Hoffman Fuel (Box 110)
        - Indian Ridge STP (Box 110)
        - Gran Prix Service (Box 111)
        - Independtne Oil Co., Inc. (Box 111)
        - Laminated Shim Co. (Box 111)
        - Lotstein Realty Co. (Box 111)
        - Luigi Chinetti Design (Box 111)
        - Lund, Herbert (Box 111)
        - Maaco Painting & Body Works (Box 111)
        - Machlett Laboratories, Inc., 5 folders (Box 111)
        - Meineke of Stamford (Box 111)
        - Metropolitan Petroleum Company (Box 111)
        - Newfield School (Box 111)
        - Nick’s Auto Body (Box 111)
        - Norotor River -- Pollution (Box 111)
        - Northeast Utilities (Box 111)
        - Oakridge Vista N.Y. (Box 111)
        - O’Brien Photo Engraving, 2 folders (Box 111)
        - Olin Corporation, 2 folders (Box 111)
        - Parkside Condominiums, 2 folders (Box 111)
        - Petrizzi, Gerald (Box 111)
        - Peckham Materials Corp. - Liquid Asphalt Terminal (Box 111)
        - Petroleum Heat & Power (Box 111)
        - Pickwick Ice Cream (Box 111)
        - Pip=s Auto Center (Box 111)
        - Pitney Bowes, 4 folders (Box 111)
        - Polycast Technology Corporation, 3 folders (Box 111)
        - Polymer Industries, Inc., 3 folders (Box 111)
        - Research Plating & Electro Forming, 2 folders (Box 111)
        - Rich-Taubman Associates (Box 111)
        - Rockrimmon Country Club (Box 111)
        - Roxbury Elementary School (Box 111)
        - Schettino, John (Box 111)
        - Sealtest Foods (Box 111)
        - Six Landmark Square (Box 111)
        - Stamford Auto Repair (Box 111)
        - Stamford Catholic High School, 4 folders (Box 111)
        - Southeast Quadrant Renewal Project (Box 112)
        - Stamford Elderly Housing (Box 112)
        - Stamford Grove Assoc. (Box 112)
        - Strome Connecticut Corp. (Box 112)
        - Stamford - Redevelopment (Box 112)
        - Stamford Harbor (Box 112)
        - Stamford Housing (Box 112)
        - Stamford Marina (Box 112)
        - Stamford Polishing & Plating, 2 folders (Box 112)
        - Stamford Yacht Club (Box 112)
        - Stephen Motor Corp. (Box 112)
        - Taubman Co. (Box 112)
        - Thermatool Co. (Box 112)
        - U.S. Surgical, 2 folders (Box 112)
        - U-Haul (Box 112)
        - Yale & Towne Mfg. (Box 112)
      - Sterling (Box 112)
        - Misc. (Box 112)
        - Coventry, RI - Haz. Waste Dump (Box 112)
        - Case and Risley Press Paper, 2 folders (Box 112)
        - Lynch, Kenneth (Box 112)
        - Storti, Edward (Box 112)
        - Revere Textile Prints, 3 folders (Box 112)
      - Stonington (Box 112)
        - Misc., 3 folders (Box 112)
        - American Velvet, 4 folders (Box 112)
        - American Velvet, 3 folders (Box 113)
        - Bindloss, Inc., 2 folders (Box 113)
        - Bob Valenti Chevy (Box 113)
        - Brustolom Buick-Pontiac (Box 113)
        - Cerro Wire & Cable Co. (Box 113)
        - Charbert Narrow Fabrics Corp. (Box 113)
        - CT Investment Caasting Corp., 4 folders (Box 113)
        - Cottrell Co. (Box 113)
        - Davis Standard (Box 113)
        - General Dynamics (Box 113)
        - George=s Auto Body (Box 113)
        - Harris Corp. (Box 113)
        - Johnson, Frank (Box 113)
        - Jones & Tate (Box 113)
        - Jung, Elizabeth (Box 113)
        - Lord’s Point, 2 folders (Box 113)
        - Marina’s (Regional) (Box 113)
        - Mason’s Island Co., 3 folders (Box 113)
        - Monsanto, 2 folders (Box 113)
        - Mystic Color Lab (Box 113)
        - Mystic Marinelife Aquarium, 4 folders (Box 113)
        - Mystic Motor Inn, 2 folders (Box 113)
        - Mystic Seaport, 2 folders (Box 113)
        - Mystic Seaport Motor Inn, 2 folders (Box 113)
        - Mystic Valley Water Co., 4 folders (Box 113)
        - Old Mystic Motor Lodge (Box 113)
        - Palmer Subdivision (Box 113)
        - Quambaug Cove Proposed Pharmaceutical Plant (Box 114)
        - Posi-Seal Int. Inc. (Box 114)
        - Puritan Lanudry (Box 114)
        - Paul & Pat Lombardi (Box 114)
        - Regional Mystic Borough-Pawatuck Municipal Sewerage, 2 folders (Box 114)
        - Rowes Laundry (Box 114)
        - Sewerage, Municipal, 3 folders (Box 114)
        - Stonington Borough Outfall Sewer, 2 folders (Box 114)
        - Sirtex Printing Div., 2 folders (Box 114)
        - SNET (Box 114)
        - Westerly Red-Mix Concrete, 2 folders (Box 114)
        - Whittaker & Yardney (Box 114)
        - Yardney Electric Corporation, 2 folders (Box 114)
      - Stratford (Box 114)
        - A&J Tire & Rubber (Box 114)
        - Automotive Restorations (Box 114)
        - Avco Lycoming, 3 folders (Box 114)
        - Refuse Disposal (Box 114)
        - Stratford Bus Line & Co. (Box 114)
        - Stratford Honda (Box 114)
        - Avco Lycoming Division (Box 115)
        - Avon Radiator Service (Box 115)
        - Beaver Dam Lake (Box 115)
        - Borden Co. (Box 115)
        - Bridgeport Rolling Mills Co., 2 folders (Box 115)
        - Bridgeport Fittings, 2 folders (Box 115)
        - Charter Arms, 2 folders (Box 115)
        - Chemical Plating Co., 2 folders (Box 115)
        - Combustion Equipment (Box 115)
        - Contract Plating, 2 folders (Box 115)
        - Copperlite (Box 115)
        - Dresser Industries, 2 folders (Box 115)
        - E.P.A. Inc. (Box 115)
        - Empire Silver (Box 115)
        - European Americal Auto Sales (Box 115)
        - Estuary, Housatonic River (Box 115)
        - Honeyspot Motors (Box 116)
        - Kramers Recycled Used Auto Parts (Box 116)
        - Micro Etch (Box 116)
        - Bridgeport Rolling Mills Co. (Box 116)
        - Mermaid Tavern (Box 116)
        - Mobil Chemical Co. Plastics Div., 2 folders (Box 116)
        - Raybestos Manhattoan, 5 folders (Box 116)
        - Ross & Roberts, 2 folders (Box 116)
        - Sikorsky Aircraft Div., 2 folders (Box 116)
        - Stratford Honda (Box 116)
        - Response Graphics (Box 116)
        - Motor Inn (Box 116)
        - Super Retread Tire Co., Inc. (Box 116)
        - Tiko Roofing Co., 3 folders (Box 116)
        - Stratford Town of (Box 116)
        - Ware Chemical Corp (Box 117)
        - Warner Hill Apts. (Box 117)
      - Suffield (Box 117)
        - Suffield Misc, 3 folders (Box 117)
        - Suffield Subsurface Problems (Box 117)
        - Doyker (Box 117)
        - Enviroland-Equestrian Community (Box 117)
        - H.P. Hood & Sons, Inc. (Box 117)
        - Klement, William (Box 117)
        - Proposed Elementary School (Box 117)
        - B.J. Ahrens, pine Manor Development (Box 117)
        - St. Alphonsus College, 2 folders (Box 117)
        - Suffield Academy (Box 117)
        - Suffield Auto Center (Box 117)
        - Suffield High School (Box 117)
        - Suffield Town Dump (Box 117)
        - Union Carbide Corp.-Linde Div., 2 folders (Box 117)
      - Thomaston (Box 117)
        - Thomaston Misc. (Box 117)
        - Thomaston Landfill (Box 117)
        - Thomaston Oil Spill Reports (Box 117)
        - ABC Better Homes (Box 117)
        - Branch Brook Camp Ground (Box 117)
        - CT Water Co. (Box 117)
        - D & J Harley Davidson (Box 117)
        - John Dolan (Box 117)
        - Donham Craft, 2 folders (Box 117)
        - Dorset Corp. (Box 117)
        - Drawn Metal Tube Co., 3 folders (Box 117)
        - Eastern Photographic, 2 folders (Box 117)
        - Eclipse Glass Co. (Box 117)
        - Envirite (Box 117)
        - Fisher’s Service Center (Box 118)
        - General Time Corp/Talley (Box 118)
        - George’s Service Station (Box 118)
        - Liqwacon Corp. (Box 118)
        - Plume & Atwood, 4 folders (Box 118)
        - Risdon Mfg. Co. (Box 118)
        - Solvents Recovery Service (Box 118)
        - Stevens Co., 2 folders (Box 118)
        - Summit Finishing, 2 folders (Box 118)
        - Tech System, 2 folders (Box 118)
        - Thomaston Special Products (Box 118)
        - Thomaston Treadwell Crop. - Hearing (Box 118)
        - Thomaston Water Co. (Box 118)
        - Whyco Chromium, 3 folders (Box 118)
      - Thompson (Box 119)
        - Thompson Misc., 2 folders (Box 119)
        - Astromatic, Inc. (Box 119)
        - Bates Auto Parts (Box 119)
        - Belding Chemical Industries, 4 folders (Box 119)
        - Best Value Mfg. Co. (Box 119)
        - Colts Plastics Co. (Box 119)
        - C. S. Allen Div. (Box 119)
        - Gansett Corp., 2 folders (Box 119)
        - Johnson Corrugated Products, 2 folders (Box 119)
        - Koinonia Sports School (Box 119)
        - Leo Ready Mix Concrete Co. (Box 119)
        - Marianapolis Preparatory School, 2 folders (Box 119)
        - Richard Marino (Box 119)
        - Oscar Norman (Box 119)
        - Ernest O’Leary (Box 119)
        - Sanitary Dash, 3 folders (Box 119)
        - Valley Textile (Box 119)
        - Villa Maria Rest Home (Box 119)
        - Whitney’s Auto Service (Box 119)
      - Tolland (Box 119)
        - Tolland Misc., 2 folders (Box 119)
        - Tolland Town Landfill (Box 119)
        - Chestnut Estates a/k/a Highridge Estates (Box 120)
        - Cone Road Subsurface System Problem (Box 120)
        - Dennis Davey (Box 120)
        - Goose I Subdivision (Box 120)
        - CL&P (Box 120)
        - Town of Tolland Fire House (Box 120)
        - Bryan Corp. (Box 120)
        - Buff Cap Hill Residential Complex (Box 120)
        - Bundy Motors (Box 120)
        - Howard Johnson’s - Hearing (Box 120)
        - Howard Johnson’s (Box 120)
        - Karon Acres (Box 120)
        - Madrid Corp., 2 folders (Box 120)
        - McCormick Acres Subdivision (Box 120)
        - Morrison Automobile (Box 120)
        - Orchard Hill Subdivision - Harkins (Box 120)
        - Quaker Knoll Village - Hearing (Box 120)
        - Santini Homes (Box 120)
        - Soucier Complaint (Box 120)
        - Tolland County Volkswagen (Box 120)
        - Tolland Ridge II (Box 120)
        - Tolland Ridge III, 2 folders (Box 120)
        - Bryan Corp - Hearing (Box 120)
      - Torrington (Box 120)
        - Torrington Misc, 3 folders (Box 120)
        - Torrington Town of (Box 120)
        - B&M Trucking Equipment (Box 120)
        - Colonial Bronze Co. (Box 120)
        - Agway (Box 120)
        - Atfas Unlimited (Box 120)
        - Arnold Robert (Box 120)
        - Art’s custom Corner (Box 120)
        - Asquared Industries (Box 120)
        - Colonial Bronze Co., 2 folders (Box 121)
        - Country Side Volkswaon, Inc. (Box 121)
        - Custom Plating & Buff (Box 121)
        - Dave’s Auto Sales (Box 121)
        - Fitzgerald Mfg. Co., 2 folders (Box 121)
        - Giannis Garage (Box 121)
        - Gotrans (Box 121)
        - Hackborth Subaru (Box 121)
        - Haydon Mfg. (Box 121)
        - Iffland Lumber Co. (Box 121)
        - KEI Merchandizing (Box 121)
        - K-Mark Plaza (Box 121)
        - Torrington Oil Spills (Box 121)
        - Migeon Motors (Box 121)
        - O & G Industries (Box 121)
        - Peerless (Box 121)
        - Pheoll of New England (Box 121)
        - Ron’s Auto Sales (Box 121)
        - Royals Garage (Box 121)
        - Schibis Auto Repair, 2 folders (Box 121)
        - Torrington Siltation & Erosion (Box 121)
        - Specialty Coatings (Box 121)
        - Stone Container Corp. (Box 121)
        - Torrington Subsurface Problems (Box 121)
        - Torin Corp., 4 folders (Box 121)
        - Torrington Co., 6 folders (Box 121)
        - Torrington Scrap, Inc. (Box 121)
        - Torrington Used Cars (Box 121)
        - Turner & Seymour Mfg. Co. (Box 121)
        - Wilson Auto Body (Box 121)
        - Turner & Seymour Mfg. Co., 2 folders (Box 122)
        - Union Hardware, 2 folders (Box 122)
        - Union tubular Products (Box 122)
        - VSH Realty (Box 122)
        - Warrenton Woolen (Box 122)
        - Wayne’s Radiator Shop (Box 122)
        - Wilson’s Datsun, 2 folders (Box 122)
        - Zeller Tire Co. (Box 122)
      - Trumbull (Box 122)
        - Trumbull Misc, 2 folders (Box 122)
        - Greater Bpt Regional Planning Agency (Box 122)
        - Brickman, Herbert (Box 122)
        - Bunker Ramo Corp., 2 folders (Box 122)
        - Cheseborough Pond, 2 folders (Box 122)
        - Combustion Equipment Corp. (Box 122)
        - Dow Corning Corp., 2 folders (Box 122)
        - Hawley Lane Co. (Box 122)
        - Knecht’s Garage (Box 122)
        - New England Printin & Lithographic (Box 122)
        - Provenzano, Paul (Box 122)
        - Trio Industrial - Hearing (Box 122)
      - Union (Box 122)
        - Union Misc (Box 122)
        - Broadway, Wesley (Box 122)
        - Salt Pine Contamination (Box 122)
      - Vernon (Box 123)
        - Vernon Misc. (Box 123)
        - Vernon Groundwater Contamination Problems (Box 123)
        - Albi Mfg., 2 folders (Box 123)
        - Aldon Spinning Mills Corp. (Box 123)
        - Amerbelle Corp. (Box 123)
        - AMF Cuno (Box 123)
        - Ano-Coil Corp, 3 folders (Box 123)
        - Ano-Coil Corp - Hearing (Box 123)
        - Compbell Aven. Well Contamination (Box 123)
        - Contromatics Corp./Mark Metal, 2 folders (Box 123)
        - Conversion Chemical, 3 folders (Box 123)
        - Cunliffe Motor Sales (Box 123)
        - Hatch Hill Estates (Box 123)
        - FEPCO (Box 123)
        - Florence Mill Assoc. (Box 123)
        - Hockanum Load Allocation (Box 123)
        - International Motor Car (Box 123)
        - LaPointe Industries, Inc., 2 folders (Box 123)
        - Leisure Living, 2 folders (Box 123)
        - Malone Residence (Box 123)
        - Mark Metal Finishing Corp., 3 folders (Box 123)
        - Manchester Plymouth (Box 123)
        - Maple Garage (Box 123)
        - Minnesota Mining & Mfg. (Box 123)
        - Precision Plating & Die Finishing Co., Inc. (Box 123)
        - Rockville Water & Aqueduct, 2 folders (Box 123)
        - Shea’s Garage (Box 123)
        - Tinson, Cort (Box 123)
        - Turnpike Travel Trailers (Box 123)
        - Stop & Go Transmission (Box 123)
        - Vernon Assoc/Nutmeg Village (Box 123)
        - Wedgewood Homes (Box 123)
        - 3M (Box 123)
      - Voluntown (Box 123)
        - Voluntown Misc., 2 folders (Box 123)
        - Eugene Gileau (Box 123)
        - Kelly Property (Box 123)
        - Wellis Maynard (Box 123)
        - Pachaug State Forest (Box 123)
        - Rytman-Jalkenon Farm (Box 123)
        - Miriam Walker Valley of the 4 Season Development, 2 folders (Box 123)
      - Wallingford (Box 124)
        - Misc, 2 folders (Box 124)
        - Town of Wallingford, 2 folders (Box 124)
        - Municipal Industrial Pollution Control Facility (Box 124)
        - Town of Wallingford - Water Division (Box 124)
        - Proposed Landfill Expansion - Barberino Site (Box 124)
        - Quinnipiac River Pollution (Box 124)
        - Ahearn Development Corporation (Box 124)
        - Allegheny Ludlum Steel, 2 folders (Box 124)
        - Americal Cyanimid, 3 folders (Box 124)
        - Auto Artisans (Box 124)
        - Barberino (Box 124)
        - Birmingham Silver Co. (Box 124)
        - Body Specialties (Box 124)
        - Bulk Treatment Service (Box 124)
        - Car Care Clinic, Inc. (Box 124)
        - W.i. Clark Co. (Box 124)
        - Discount Tire Center (Box 124)
        - East Real Estate Services (Box 124)
        - Executive Auto (Box 124)
        - Eyelet Specialty, 3 folders (Box 124)
        - Fine Car Engineering Studios (Box 124)
        - George's Waste Oil (Box 124)
        - Georgia Pacific (Box 124)
        - Glass Industries (Box 124)
        - Glen Count Apartments (Box 124)
        - Goldfeder Silverware Comany, Inc., 2 folders (Box 124)
        - Grinold Truck Equipment (Box 124)
        - Gello Bros. (Box 124)
        - International Silver Co. (Box 124)
        - Kenyon Marine (Box 124)
        - P.b. Mutrie Trans. Corp. (Box 124)
        - New Haven Trap Rock (Box 124)
        - Maaco/avery Enterprises (Box 125)
        - Mackenzie Water Filtraton Plant (Box 125)
        - New England Farmhouse Estates (Box 125)
        - New Haven Trap Rock, 2 folders (Box 125)
        - North Colony Road Shopping Plaza (Box 125)
        - Oak Street (Box 125)
        - Peoples Garage (Box 125)
        - Pilgrim's Harbor Condos, 2 folders (Box 125)
        - Porto's Texaco Service (Box 125)
        - Quantam Incorporated (Box 125)
        - Regal Steel, Inc. (Box 125)
        - Revere Corp. Of America, 3 folders (Box 125)
        - Rose's Bus Service (Box 125)
        - Smitty's Automatic Transmission Service (Box 125)
        - Stanley (Box 125)
        - Stanley-judd Company (Box 125)
        - Stelma, Inc. (Box 125)
        - Steve's Auto Body (Box 125)
        - Stone Safety (Box 125)
        - Times Wire and Cable Company (Box 125)
        - Total Performance (Box 125)
        - Transco of Wallingford (Box 125)
        - Ulbrich Stainless Steels (Box 125)
        - Unimax Switch (Box 125)
        - Underpass Auto Parts (Box 125)
        - Valley View Subdivision (Box 125)
        - Union Carbide (Box 125)
        - Wallace Silversmiths-Wallace & Sons Mfg. Co., 2 folders (Box 125)
        - Wallingford Auto (Box 125)
        - Wallingford Radiator Service (Box 125)
        - Wallingford Steel Company (a.k.a. Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp.) (Box 125)
        - Woodland Hill Subdivision (Box 125)
        - Yalesville Silver (Box 125)
      - Warren (Box 126)
        - Misc., 2 folders (Box 126)
        - Alwin Construction, 3 folders (Box 126)
        - Arrow Pt Report (Box 126)
        - Diamond, Arnold (Box 126)
        - Eden, R.j. (Box 126)
        - Fryer, George (Box 126)
        - Gally, John (Box 126)
        - Geffken, R.h. (Box 126)
        - Hamilton, Allan (Box 126)
        - Hopkins Winery (Box 126)
        - Inn at Lake Waramaug (Box 126)
        - Isselee, J.a., 2 folders (Box 126)
        - Johnston, Stuart (Box 126)
        - Kahl, William (Box 126)
        - Lake Waramaug Hearing, 5 folders (Box 126)
        - Loughley, Richard (Box 126)
        - Quigley, Wesley, 2 folders (Box 126)
        - Sacannicandro, Fred (Box 126)
        - Sprier, Allan (Box 126)
        - Tanner, Arthur (Box 126)
        - Tanner Dairy Farm (Box 126)
        - Viola, Ronald, 2 folders (Box 126)
        - Waramaug Lake Inn (Box 126)
      - Washington (Box 126)
        - Misc, 2 folders (Box 126)
        - Siltation & Erosion (Box 126)
        - Subsurface Problems (Box 126)
        - American Indian Institute (Box 126)
        - Gunnery School (Box 126)
        - Racing International (Box 126)
      - Waterbury (Box 127)
        - Waterbury Misc, 3 folders (Box 127)
        - Waterbury, Town Of, 2 folders (Box 127)
        - Waterbury Sewage Treatment Plant (Box 127)
        - Fishkill, 1966 August 4 (Box 127)
        - Oil Spill Reports (Box 127)
        - Environmental Waste Removal, Inc. - P.h. (Box 127)
        - Selections Lts - P.h. (Box 127)
        - Thinsheet Metals Co. - P.h. (Box 127)
        - Torrington Co. - P.h. (Box 127)
        - Ct Steel & Wire Co. - P.h. (Box 127)
        - Siltation & Erosion (Box 127)
        - American Chain & Cable Co., 2 folders (Box 127)
        - American Chem. & Refining Co., 3 folders (Box 127)
        - American Electroproducts, 3 folders (Box 127)
        - American Fastener (Box 127)
        - Ambion Corp. (Box 128)
        - Anchor Fasteners, 3 folders (Box 128)
        - Anthony's Auto Sales (Box 128)
        - Automotive Appearance (Box 128)
        - Bristol Babcock, Inc. (Box 128)
        - Berke Mfg. Co. (Box 128)
        - Better Formed Metals Co., 2 folders (Box 128)
        - Bill's Auto Service (Box 128)
        - Blake & Johnson (Box 128)
        - Broadview Acres (Box 128)
        - Burndy/bantam Products (Box 128)
        - Calabrese Construction Company (Box 128)
        - Tony Calabro & Sons, 2 folders (Box 128)
        - Century Brass(formerly Scovill), 2 folders (Box 128)
        - Chase Brass & Copper Company, 5 folders (Box 128)
        - Chromium Corp. Of America (Box 128)
        - City Automatic Transmission Service (Box 128)
        - C & L Foreign Car Repair (Box 128)
        - Colony Garage (Box 128)
        - Connecticut Electroplating, 3 folders (Box 128)
        - Ct Manufacturing Co. Inc. (Box 128)
        - Conn. Steel & Wire, 3 folders (Box 128)
        - Consolidated Electronic Ind. (Box 128)
        - Consolidated Tube Fab. Corp., 2 folders (Box 128)
        - Cly-del Mfg. Co. (Box 128)
        - Colonial Sand & Gravel (Box 128)
        - Craftsman Litho (Box 128)
        - C. Service & Co. (Box 128)
        - Dot Fastener Company (Box 129)
        - Eastern Color Print (Box 129)
        - Eastern Wrecker Sales (Box 129)
        - Environmental Waste Removal, 4 folders (Box 129)
        - Epac Company, 3 folders (Box 129)
        - Ethyl Metal Fabrications (Box 129)
        - Exxon Car Wash (Box 129)
        - Fairmont Corporation of Connecticut (Box 129)
        - Family Cycle Center (Box 129)
        - Ferrule Mfg. Corp. (Box 129)
        - Firestone Tire & Rubber (Box 129)
        - Fleischer Finishing, 2 folders (Box 129)
        - Foreign Car Nursery, Inc. (Box 129)
        - Four Star Tire Center (Box 129)
        - Franks Garage (Box 129)
        - Gallagher & Gallagher (Box 129)
        - Galaxy Motors (Box 129)
        - Gasparri Sales & Repair (Box 129)
        - Green Valley Developers (Box 129)
        - Harper Leader, 4 folders (Box 129)
        - Haydon Switch & Instruments (Box 129)
        - Highland Mfg. Co., 2 folders (Box 129)
        - Industrial Overall Co., 3 folders (Box 129)
        - I-84 Reconstruction (Box 129)
        - Interstate Diesel Terminal (Box 129)
        - J&e Equipment Service (Box 129)
        - Johnny's Auto Body (Box 129)
        - Johnson Metal Hose, 3 folders (Box 129)
        - King's Auto Body & Painting Co. (Box 129)
        - Kolman Luria & Son, Inc. (Box 129)
        - Konover, David (Box 129)
        - Lakewood Metal Products (Box 129)
        - Lea Manufacturing Company, 3 folders (Box 129)
        - Leverty & Hurley Co. (Box 129)
        - Luckey's Auto Sales (Box 129)
        - Macdermid, Inc., 5 folders (Box 129)
        - Mallory Battery Co., 3 folders (Box 129)
        - Martinelli Motors, Inc. (Box 129)
        - Mattatuck Mfg. Co., 3 folders (Box 130)
        - Michael's Automotive (Box 130)
        - Miller Co., 3 folders (Box 130)
        - Mirror Polishing & Plating, 2 folders (Box 130)
        - Nutech Precision Metals (Box 130)
        - Ortale's Auto (Box 130)
        - Paint Specialty & Auto Body (Box 130)
        - Paper Delivery, Inc. (Box 130)
        - Paul's Car Wash (Box 130)
        - Plasma Coatings, Inc. (Box 130)
        - Platt Bros. & Co., 3 folders (Box 130)
        - Producton Finishing Co., 2 folders (Box 130)
        - Reidville Auto Sales (Box 130)
        - Risdon Mfg. Co., 3 folders (Box 130)
        - Robertshaw Controls, 2 folders (Box 130)
        - Rosa Auto Sales (Box 130)
        - Scoville Mfg., 2 folders (Box 130)
        - Setaro Motors (Box 130)
        - Sherwood Medical Industries (Box 131)
        - Small Lot Plating, 3 folders (Box 131)
        - Smith, Howard Bus Sales (Box 131)
        - Somers Thin Strip (Box 131)
        - Speedy Muffler King (Box 131)
        - Steele & Johnson Mfg. Co. (Box 131)
        - Superior Homes, Inc. (Box 131)
        - Tiffany Products, Inc., 2 folders (Box 131)
        - Thinsheet Metals, 2 folders (Box 131)
        - Tom's Diesel Service (Box 131)
        - Tony's Road Service (Box 131)
        - Tony's Auto Sales, 2 folders (Box 131)
        - Torrington Co. (Box 131)